<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mac Phillips</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mac Phillips</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python or R? You don&#39;t have to choose!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/python-or-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/python-or-r/</guid>
      <description>Why is this significant? Python is a widely-used coding language employed for a variety of purposes in computer science. In my Computational Biology class, we used Python and R in very similar ways, and in doing so learned how the two languages may be able to accomplish similar end goals, but they still each have certain strengths over the other.
These respective strengths and weaknesses across different tasks in both languages may be a cause for concern when it comes to certain projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Police Killings</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Selecting DataThe dataset that I will be exploring is called “police_killings” and was accessed through the fivethirtyeight database.
library(fivethirtyeight)## Warning: package &amp;#39;fivethirtyeight&amp;#39; was built under R version 3.6.3## Some larger datasets need to be installed separately, like senators and## house_district_forecast. To install these, we recommend you install the## fivethirtyeightdata package by running:## install.packages(&amp;#39;fivethirtyeightdata&amp;#39;, repos =## &amp;#39;https://fivethirtyeightdata.github.io/drat/&amp;#39;, type = &amp;#39;source&amp;#39;)police_killings&amp;lt;-police_killingspolice_killings&amp;lt;-na.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Candidate Stories</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Selecting DataI searched the fivethirtyeight R package and found two datasets about mentions of 2020 democratic presidential candidates in cable and online news. The datasets contain information categorized by candidate and by day, and include statistics on how many stories each candidate was featured in as well as the percentage of stories that each was present in on any given day. These datasets caught my attention as I have been curious about the influence of media and news coverage on politics, specifically elections, for the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  --</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
